You're a polka dot. That [music] outfit
was so cool.
I just got back and showered from 8:00
a.m. Pilates class. Feeling good,
feeling productive. My legs are actual
jelly. That class
was very glute focused. I can't believe
I'm already a quarter of the way into
the semester. I feel like I just blinked
and now I have like
four assignments due in 2 weeks, so I
need to lock in. I'm going to quickly
get ready and head to a cafe downstairs
to get breakfast and a coffee before my
class. I have a fashion studio class. I
think this semester I have the most
interesting um units and assignments so
far. I have to create an entire brand
for my assignment. I need to come up
with logos, clothing tags, and
everything. It's pretty exciting, but
just a lot of things to do and I just
haven't done any of them, so
it's kind of cooked.
This is my outfit for today.
Yeah, this is from Aritzia. This is from
Glassons. This is from Ruby Merlot, but
I'm pretty sure they discontinued it. A
lot of people ask me where this bag is
from.
It's from Ruby Merlot, but
yeah, they don't have it anymore,
unfortunately, but they do have a lot of
other really cool stuff, so go check
them out anyways.
This video is proudly sponsored by
Amber. So, I know a lot of you guys are
very interested [music] in studying
abroad because you might be a study
abroad student yourself or you're
planning to study abroad in the future.
And one of the most stressful things,
other than the university applications,
is student accommodation. [music] And
that definitely was the case for me
because the months leading up to coming
here, I was scouring the internet all
day, every day to look for student
[music] accommodation. And I wish I knew
about Amber before because Amber is a
platform exclusively for students to
look for accommodation, utilities
[music] included. That's right, it's
all-inclusive, electricity, water, and
rent. So, you don't have to worry about
extra payments. There are zero hidden
fees. [music] You get exactly what you
pay for. It is super easy to search cuz
you can just filter it by locality and
university. And don't worry, all the
listings are verified for your [music]
safety. There are only three simple
steps. Just click the link in my
description box, browse, inquire, and
someone from Amber will contact you
immediately [music] to help you out. So,
if you are planning to study abroad and
want a hassle-free experience, just
click the link in the description box
for special student housing discounts.
Thank you, Amber, for sponsoring this
video, and now back to the vlog.
>> Table one.
>> [music]
>> This is a chicken on rye toast sandwich.
I always get this when I get
I always get this when I come here. And
this is a flat white on skim milk.
>> [music]
>> Flat white on skim.
>> Oh, okay.
>> [music]
>> Okay.
[music]
>> I just got home and I got all my stuff
and I'm going to go head out again to go
grocery shopping cuz I have nothing in
the fridge.
>> [music]
>> I have a work shift in an hour.
So, I'm going to have a quick yogurt
bowl before that. I'm going to have a
quick yogurt bowl
before my shift so I don't like
>> [music]
[music]
>> I actually spent way longer in the
grocery store than I thought I would. I
only wanted to buy yogurt and fruits and
then here I am. I don't know if they
don't sell the [music] tubs anymore, but
I have to buy the individually packed
ones. I got blueberry and vanilla. I got
strawberries [music]
and they were on sale. I'm pretty sure
this is mozzarella. Not sure what kind
of cheese this is, but
the one with more protein. And I really
like this cuz it melts really well. I
got chicken thigh fillets,
tomatoes, [music]
green capsicum,
blueberries.
I got corn, like these mission wraps. I
got the mini ones cuz I feel like the
big ones are so huge. A pack of baby
spinach. I'll quickly wash my [music]
fruits, cut them up, and then eat my
yogurt bowl. I have 20 minutes to do
this and then get up to work.
>> [music]
>> Strawberries are my favorite fruit ever,
but it's so expensive in Malaysia. But
here, [music]
it's always in the fridge, always.
Hello guys, I just got back from work.
I'm so tired. It is 9:45 and I still
have to make dinner. I'm going to
meal prep the chicken in advance so I
can just make this wrap way easier and
quicker next time.
>> [music]
>> So, I packed my lunch. I packed some
berries and a wrap.
>> [music]
[music]
>> And actually, a new cafe that opened on
campus, so I'm going to go check it out.
I think the drinks look really good,
[music] but I'm just going to get a
chocolate cuz I need that right now.
Like, I feel like dying now fighting all
the demons, trying not to sleep [music]
in class.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I'm just sitting here waiting for my
friend Angeli to get to campus [music]
cuz we have a class together.
And then she's going to get lunch. So
I'm going to accompany her. I'm low key
[music] fried. Brain is fried. I was
sitting at the cafe earlier and I think
like the sleep deprivation plus caffeine
[music] like hit me and I felt like so
anxious and jittery. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hello guys, I am home now. I actually
wanted to stay at the library until
8:00, but my laptop died at like
6:00-ish.
So, I just ate dinner and then came
home. I'm also really exhausted from
today. It was a long
long day for me. But, let's do my skin
care. So, this is the toner pad that I'm
using. This is from A'PIEU. It is the
Glutathione toner pad. This is the serum
that I use. This is the Skin1004, or
also known as Skin Chosol. This is the
Madagascar Centella Asiatica Fresh N
Pure.
I go in with the Anua Azelaic Acid.
And for moisturizer, I use this 345
Relief Cream from Dr. Althea.
And that is my skin care routine.
Yeah, good night, guys. I'm so tired.
So, I missed my Pilates class. I could
not wake up at 6:30. I think I snoozed
three alarms, and then I woke up at 6:40
and I was like, "Oh, shit." So, I'm
going to get ready, um, have breakfast,
and go get coffee, I think. Yeah. I'm
all ready now. I'm going to put jewelry
before I head out. I'm wearing like a
long-sleeve thing, so I'm going to put
it over my shirt.
>> [music]
>> Whatever. Who cares? Who cares?
I look
so much more like
put together now. Don't know if I want
to have breakfast just outside or eat my
yogurt at home.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I am finally I back home. I am [music]
so
So, I got three pieces of thrift
clothing. I didn't want to go too crazy
because actually it's not that cheap
compared to Malaysia. [music]
Like, why was this
$12? But, I really like the fabric. Look
at the color. And then I got these
jeans. Yeah, I really like the color of
this and I think I can do really cool
patchwork this fabric. And then I saw
this one, this crazy ass top.
It's like a tank top inside and it's
sewn together. [music] So, it has like a
bubble effect at the hem. And I got this
sheer polka dot fabric. It was so cool.
But, I also went to this shop called The
Fabric Store. If you guys watch [music]
my uni vlogs, you know that I go there
pretty often to get my fabrics. And uh
students [music] get five free samples
every time we go. But, this mint one,
this is 100% polyester
>> [music]
>> satin. This is a more blue mint color.
This is a like a sweatpants fabric.
Can you see where I'm going with the
colors? I love these [music] colors. And
then I have this baby pinkish, more a
little bit purply. This is 100% [music]
silk. And then I got this It looks white
almost, but it's a light blue.
I forgot what [snorts] material this was
called, but it's like a
thick cotton. Then I got a little bit of
this kind of lace.
>> [music]